

# **CARLOS HUGUET**

SENIOR IT ENGINEER

# **INTEREST AND HOBBIES**

I'm a nice person who loves travel, play soccer with friends on tuesdays and play video games. In addition, I like to cook and I have taken some lessons about cooking.

However my passion is the photography, when I travel, I always take my camera and try to get nice pics.

## **SKILLS & ABILITIES**

- People management
- Providers relationship
- Fluent english (B2)

## **CONTACT INFORMATION**

Cell: +34 66 00 33 434 email: huguet10@gmail.com Website: https://chuguet.github.io GitHub: https://github.com/chuguet LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/chuguet

# **ABOUT ME**

Software Engineer with a Masters in Web Engineering from the Polytechnic University of Madrid and a passion for Computer Science. I have worked in the analysis, design and architecture of web applications for important companies in sports betting and banking sectors.

In the last years I have oriented and developed my professional career towards the banking sector along with the development of software and web engineering, realizing successful projects across leading websites and pioneers in the current market.

KAIZEN (Today better than yesterday, tomorrow better than today)

# **PROFESSIONAL HISTORY**

# **Denizen Financial at BBVA SA**

EU Team Lead (mar. 2019 - currently)

Software IT Architect (may. 2018 - mar. 2019)

Senior IT Engineer (aug. 2016 - may. 2018)

#### **ING Bank**

Full stack developer (jun. 2014 - jul. 2016)

#### **Factoria ETSIA SL**

Senior programmer (jan. 2012 - may. 2014)

# Coritel

Junior programmer (aug. 2011 - dec. 2011)

# **EDUCATIONAL HISTORY**

## **Masters in Web Engineering**

Polytechnic University of Madrid (2014 - 2015)

## **Software Engineer Degree**

Pontifical University of Salamanca (2012 - 2014)

# **Technical Software Engineer Degree**

University of Málaga (2007 - 2011)